var questionList = [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What is capital of Maharashtra?",
        "option": ["Mumbai", "Nagpur", "Pune", "Solapur"],
        "answer": "Mumbai"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What is Capital of Madhya Pradesh?",
        "option": ["Bhopal", "Jabalpur", "Indore", "Gwalier"],
        "answer": "Bhopal"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is the capital of Arunachal Pradesh?",
        "option": ["Itanagar", "Dispur", "Imphal", "Shillong"],
        "answer": "Itanagar"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which state has Almond as its State Tree?",
        "option": ["Himachal Pradesh", "Goa", "Jammu and Kashmir", "Arunachal Pradesh"],
        "answer": "Jammu and Kashmir"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which state has the largest area?",
        "option": ["Maharashtra", "Madhya Pradesh", "Jammu and Kashmir", "Rajasthan"],
        "answer": "Rajasthan"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which state has the largest population?",
        "option": ["Maharashtra", "Uttar Pradesh", "Bihar", "Andra Pradesh"],
        "answer": "Uttar Pradesh"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "In what state are the Elephant Falls located?",
        "option": ["Mizoram", "Orissa", "Manipur", "Meghalaya"],
        "answer": "Meghalaya"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "In which state is the main language Khasi?",
        "option": ["Mizoram", "Nagaland", "Meghalaya", "Tripura"],
        "answer": "Meghalaya"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What is the state flower of Haryana?",
        "option": ["Lotus", "Rhododendron", "Golden Shower", "Not declared"],
        "answer": "Lotus"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "What are the major languages spoken in Andhra Pradesh?",
        "option": ["English and Telugu", "Telugu and Urdu", "Telugu and Kannada", "All of the above languages"],
        "answer": "Telugu and Urdu"
    }
];